[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A car that gets over 200 miles per gallon is reclaimed by the factory, after its owner calls to congratulate the manufacturers about its excellent performance.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This French soccer player, who in 2001 was transferred from Italian team, Juventus to Spanish club, Real Madrid, won the 2003 FIFA World Player of the Year Award.", "correct_answer": "Zinedine Zidane", "incorrect_answers": ["Thierry Henry", "Jean-Pierre Papin", "Robert Pires"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Too much rainfall can kill plants, just like a drought.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What should a stranger say when seeing a baby less that an year old according to Russian tradition?", "correct_answer": "Oh, what an ugly child!", "incorrect_answers": ["They should not speak or smile", "May you grow tall and healthy!", "May God guide your way!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this movie Ray Millands character, who suffers a writer\u2019s block, scours his apartment for that bottle of rye he just doesn\u2019t remember finishing.", "correct_answer": "The Lost Weekend", "incorrect_answers": ["Dial M. For Murder", "Double Indemnity", "Days of Wine and Roses"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This extraordinary marine mammal is often considered a whale, but it is actually a dolphin.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Killer Whale", "Blackfish", "Seawolf"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what structure are S.P.E.C.T.R.E.s headquarters located, in the 1967 movie, You Only Live Twice?", "correct_answer": "Volcano", "incorrect_answers": ["Pyramid", "Monastery", "Buddhist Temple"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Badwater basin, the lowest point in North America, is located in which US valley?", "correct_answer": "Death Valley", "incorrect_answers": ["Sun Valley", "Big Smoky Valley", "Hudson Valley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was baseball announcer Joe Garagiolas best friend in childhood ?", "correct_answer": "Yogi Berra", "incorrect_answers": ["Stan Musial", "Red Barber", "Chris Schenkel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor, who won a Tony for Inherit the Wind in 1956, played the racist who was Juror #10 in 12 Angry Men.", "correct_answer": "Ed Begley Sr.", "incorrect_answers": ["Lee J. Cobb", "E. G. Marshall", "Henry Fonda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The third largest landowner in New York City.", "correct_answer": "New York University", "incorrect_answers": ["Donald Trump", "City Council", "NYPD"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie National Treasure, the first piece of the puzzle in the search for the treasure was a pipe. Where was it found?", "correct_answer": "In a ship", "incorrect_answers": ["In a pyramid", "In the clock tower under Big Ben", "In the Lincolns bedroom"]}]